Over 50 per cent of Indian
online gaming start-ups
experienced revenue decline
due to a 28 per cent GST
hike imposed last year.
Only five out of 12 surveyed
companies reported revenue
growth, while seven faced
de-growth or stagnation.
The new GST led to funding
challenges, reduced
growth, job losses, and
increased uncertainty.
4 companies have not
secured funding and
may exit the sector if
taxes aren't normalised.
Three companies are facing
financial difficulties and
are considering selling.
The high tax rate has made it
difficult for even profitable
start-ups to sustain margins.
Several gaming start-ups,
including Gamescraft and
Deltacorp, have received
substantial GST notices.